Well...
I was surprised to hear that a well-known person came to make his debut today.
That's right. The immediate junior.
Naotsugu's junior. It's like a subordinate of the immediate successor. Like a subordinate in a company.
It's different from the other staffers' children.
I feel even more uncomfortable. Even more so.
Ah, Naotsugu's subordinates.
Oh, welcome.
With his subordinate.
Then, please introduce your sister.
Yes, this is everyone from Ukka. Pleased to meet you.
Pleased to meet you.
These are Naotsugu's men?
Naotsugu's men.
Yes, Uka's men.
Welcome at Carnaidrib.
A group of six members belonging to Stardust Planet, the same group as Ebichu.
Uka will be releasing their major debut mini-album, Seishun Shosetsu, on November 16th.
Yes, I'm Ayami Kawase, a TVK lover from Kanagawa Prefecture, please!
Thank you!
I'm from Tokyo and sometimes visit Kanagawa Prefecture.
I'm Yuukirina.
I'm from Tokyo, but I go to Kanagawa Prefecture once in a while.
I'm from Tokyo, but I go to Kanagawa sometimes.
I'm Ruri Aoi and I'm from Kanagawa Prefecture.
I often come to Kanagawa Prefecture, or rather, I live there.
I'd appreciate it if you could help me.
You're from your hometown?
Yes, I'm Maasa Serizawa from Tokyo.
I also like Kanagawa Prefecture.
People from Kanagawa and Tokyo have similar letters.
Yes.
I'm Director Murahoshi from Saitama.
A lot of people come from Kanagawa.
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes, it's all right, isn't it?
Yes, yes.
I'm Akane Sora from Kanagawa Prefecture.
Kanagawa Prefecture is mine.
It's not yours.
I said it plainly.
It belongs to everyone.
So, since we're here, I'd like to do a survey.
I'd like to know who among the members of Ebichu you get along with or seem to get along with.
I don't care if it's imaginary.
I'd like to ask you a few questions.
Who do you like or think you like among the members of Ebichu?
Or Mr. Kawase?
Yes, Ms. Kawase.
Mirei Hoshino.
I think she and Ayame are the most compatible.
I see.
I go out to dinner with Ayame and stuff.
That's right.
She's been dropping me lines.
Is he normally like this?
He's a senior.
He's a senior?
He's a senior. And he's got a refreshing personality, doesn't he, Mirei?
I'm also very easy to talk to.
That's great!
You serve her meals, right?
She's serving them.
Thanks for the food.
Sis.
Thank you.
You're so cool.
That's a subordinate.
They're my precious, precious subordinates.
I'd like to train a lot of them.
I, on the other hand, am always treated by you, so...
I'm his subordinate.
You work for him?
By the way, I treat you all the time.
That's why you're like this.
Like this.
That means I'm the one treating all your men, right?
That's not what it means.
We're connected.
It's a proximate connection.
It's fine.
But they grew up together.
We're all connected.
Yes, yes...
Then, Murahoshi.
Murahoshi is Kaho Kobayashi and Yamanashi Nakayamiko.
They look a bit alike.
Really? I'm so happy.
Hanaho and Riko are close in age.
Last year, there was a live concert where Stardust idols gathered.
I talked a lot with Hanaho and Riko there.
I wanted to talk with them more.
They are fun people.
Pleasant people.
I really am.
Yes, next, Akane-san.
Yes, Akane-san.
I have dinner with Kashiwagi Hyuga-chan, and we are good friends.
I see.
And I often go to Hanaho-chan's birthday party.
Really?Heh.
What about you, Hanaho?
By the way, I mean Hinata-chan.
I call him Bakumida Shoyo.
Shoyo is the one who takes care of invitations and stuff like that, right?
Say, "This store...
Thank you
Oh!
Thank you!
Oh, you guys are all so mature!
What's up with that?
Don't you get a chance to buy me a drink or something and act like I'm a senior too?
Okay, next.
Serizawa-san!
I'd like to talk to Riko Nakayama.
And I'd also like to talk to Cocona Sakuragi, who's the same age as you.
She's the same age as Namichi?
Yes, but we haven't talked much.
So I'm wondering what kind of personality she has.
Riko, I haven't talked to you very much.
I've been told I'm pretty strange.
I don't know if you're weird, but I think you're mysterious, so I'm curious about you.
We'll have a lot of opportunities to talk.
I guess so.
Next, Murahoshi.
Okay, I'll go.
Murasei.
Well...
I said...
Yuuki
I'm here.
I'm sorry
Yes, yes, yes...
Maybe there are two of them.
One with the same name...
Aoi.
Yes, yes, yes.
Ms. Aoi, Yuno-chan.
I like gummy bears.
Yuno-chan eats a lot of gummy bears too.
I've heard your recommendations, so I think we'd be a good match.
Gummy friend
I think he only eats gummy bears and seaweed.
He can eat gummy bears all the time.
And last but not least, Yuki-san.
Yes, sir.
I heard you're good at short-distance running, so I thought maybe you like to exercise.
I'd like to run with her.
I'd like that.
Let's run together.
That's the spirit.
I'm good at running.
I like running and I'm very athletic.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I see.
So I'm hoping to get into some battles.
You know, like, who's the fastest in a dash-off.
And we could run forever and see who runs out first.
Poor, poor, poor.
I'd like to see that.
Hey.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.